What was it that you really saw in
Spencer that you know stood out that
made him kind of the guy you guys wanted
there?
>> Character, athleticism, toughness.
>> Todd, where does he play on the line?
>> Left tackle.
>> You are you concerned that he hasn't
played that in a couple years at all?
>> Uh, no.
>> Why not? uh ended up where they as he
moved over to right tackle, they played
Caleb over on that side. So now he's
going to play left tackle for us.
>> Yeah. Well,
>> so what's it like your first draft as a
head coach? What's his experience?
>> Well, we were jacked. I mean, to be able
to move back three spots, pick up a
third and a fifth. What a great job by
Andrew and get the player we targeted
the whole time. And uh I mean we
couldn't be any more excited and still
have another pick later on tonight.
>> Jordan Tyson was still on the board and
you guys made the trade down. So
obviously then Spencer must have been
your guys's number one.
>> No, we targeted Spencer.
>> With Spencer being the first tackle the
word, what was it about him that you
thought separated him from the rest of
this pretty deep tackle class? As I
said, his his character was first. I
mean, the way he's wired, I think the
expectations that we'll have for him
won't even match that he has for himself
and his athleticism, his toughness.
When you want to start off the first
year of your regime, I mean, when you
start about you talk about what you
want, character, toughness, athleticism,
he has it all.
>> There was a lot of speculation
throughout the draft process that
Spencer might um move in inside the
guarder center just because of the the
arm length. What did you see on film
that alleviates the concerns about um
you know arm length attack position?
>> Well, I think his athleticism and his
toughness I I just think all of the
above. I mean I do I think that's a part
of it. Reach of course that is arm
length. Of course it is. But there's
other things that that are involved with
other characteristics that go into that.
I think he'd be an elite guard as well.
I think he'd be elite center. I don't
care where you put him. I think he's
going to be an elite player. Todd, you
you know what George Warhoff wants in
his lineman. Does does Spencer Fano fit
it better than the others?
>> I won't speak to where we had the other
guys at. I'll just say that we were
excited as heck to be able to get
Spencer
>> Andrew set a tackle tackle, but the fact
that Spencer played left early on in
Utah. Is that important for you guys to
see?
>> It's part of the equation. Yes.
those Utah teams. I mean, their
physicality is is sort of has always
been sort of their calling card. I mean,
how much does that, you know, that that
program DNA, you know, do you see in in
in Spencer and how much was that an
attractive, you know, part of that?
>> A big piece of it. You go all the way
back to Urban Meyer and then coach
Whittingham. I mean, when you get a
player from Utah, I mean, you get a
player that's physical. They're going to
practice physical. They're going to play
physical. their style, their
expectations of their old lineman. So,
uh, again, we're fired up.
>> Would you would still like to get a
receiver pretty high in this in this
draft if you can?
>> Sure.
>> And we we we'd like to add There's a
number of areas we'd like to add to our
team. That'd be one of them.
>> Were you guys at all surprised with how
the board fell previous to your guys'
pick?
>> I wouldn't say that. Um,
I think it fell pretty close within
reason. Uh, as far as I could tell being
in there with Andrew and his group, it
fell off the board the way it it
appeared to me that it was going to go.
>> Did you Spencer in for 30 minutes visit?
Because I know that was
>> we did.
>> Okay.
>> We did.
>> What's that during that
>> everything that I've already said? I
mean, it's it's it's pretty easy that uh
you know, I mean, I'm
>> now that you have Spencer Fan as your
left tackle, does it affect the movement
of any other positions on your line that
we saw the other day?
>> Not what we saw the other day was really
who we had, you know, with Elton being
out, um Titus being a little bit limited
and trying to put all the pieces
together. Ultimately, once the draft is
over, um, and free agency and we go to
camp, then we'll work on exactly where
everybody's going to fit. That was here
the other day.
>> Um, you came in and talked a lot of just
about how it all kind of starts on the
offensive line. You mentioned that, I
know, at the combine. Um, with what the
resources you guys spent in free agency
to sort of bolster that group, now your
first pick is as a tackle. Was this kind
of when you came in and took this job,
what you envisioned as you thought about
kind of rebuilding this offense that it
would start with with figuring out that
>> 100%.